# Hari Munirathnam CRM Specialist/Strategist

#### My Contact

5790hari@gmail.com

**(** +91 9741196144

Rajajinagar, Bangalore

#### **Skills**

- CRM tools
- Vendor Management tools
- Asset management.
- Data quality and inspection.
- Configuration management tools.
- Trend modeling.
- Informatica platform tools.
- Ticketing / Tracing
- Product Requirement Analysis

#### Strength

- · Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Ability to learn from mistakes
- · Assessing the needs of customers
- · Engaging personality
- Leadership

### **Education Background**

- PAMCC 2014
   Aptech Aviation & Academy
- B.Com 2013
   National Institute of Management
- Pre University 2009
   National Institute of Management
- SSLC High School 2007
   Boston International high school

#### **About Me**

Highly dedicated and professional Customer Relations Specialist with over 6.5+ experience with an outstanding record of providing superb customer service. Adept at handling multiple simultaneous service requests with complete accuracy and courtesy. Excellent mentor and trainer for new or less experienced customer service representatives.

#### **Professional Experience**

#### **Lowes E-Commerce**

AUG 2019 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Looked at improving Lowes's search strategy, product testing, and stock and inventory validation.
- Suggest fixes and improvements based on the above information

#### rBoomerang E-Commerce

Aug 2017-AUG 2019

Key responsibilities:

- Data validation, Stock validation, Product matching, Price comparison, Image Search, Validation, Quantity comparison, Product Testing, improved product listing for Lowes compared to the US-based Amazon, Wal-Mart and Home deport.
- Consult with the management team to develop long-term commercial plans
- Suggest fixes and improvements based on the above information

# Lyca Cargos- West Africa (Aviation Executive) June 2016-June 2017

Key responsibilities:

- Working with key stakeholders and vendors to establish annual goals/objectives and monitoring progress throughout the year, including providing course-correction guidance as warranted to guarantee agreed service.
- Educating and partnering with Process Owners to conduct Initial risk assessments on Third Parties during the on-boarding process and ongoing risk assessments through the duration of the Third Party relationship.

## Air Pegasus, Bangalore Airport (Customer Service Associate) Nov 2015-June 2016

Key responsibilities:

- Looked at Reservation, Ticketing, and refund assistance to passengers.
- Handled customer grievance redressal.

#### **Achievements**

2021-2022	Attended trainings and certifications in
	Lowe's Internal training program.
2015 - 2016	Best Employee award for the month of

2015 – 2016 Best Employee award for the month
Jan 2016 in Air Pegasus